[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Alan Carr movie was the first movie to win the Razzie for Years Worst Movie.", "correct_answer": "Cant Stop the Music", "incorrect_answers": ["Grease", "Magic Night", "Grease 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The plot of the 1968 Stanley Kubrick movie 2001: A Space Odyssey involves a space mission to which planet of the Solar system?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Pluto", "Uranus", "Mercury"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Muslim country was recognized as a candidate for accession in the EU on December 12th, 1999 at the Helsinki summit of the European Council?", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Israel", "Morocco", "Syria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pat Robertson, the host of the 700 Club TV program, stated that Hurricane Katrina was caused by Gods anger over the selection of lesbian comedienne Ellen Degeneres to host the upcoming Emmy Awards.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What organs do cockroaches use for the purpose of respiration?", "correct_answer": "Tracheae", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Gills", "Lungs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these islands is the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea?", "correct_answer": "Sicily", "incorrect_answers": ["Malta", "Corfu", "Cyprus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many children does Ron White have from his first wife?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "0", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the policeman and the cab driver in the movie Its a Wonderful Life?", "correct_answer": "Bert and Ernie", "incorrect_answers": ["Dave and Bill", "Steven and Casey", "Joe and Jim"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celestial formations are considered to be the birthplaces of stars?", "correct_answer": "Nebulae", "incorrect_answers": ["Galactic halos", "Spiral galaxies", "Galaxy cluster clouds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest city in California?", "correct_answer": "Los Angeles", "incorrect_answers": ["Sacramento", "Long Beach", "San Diego"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these famous people  was not an epileptic?", "correct_answer": "Otto von Bismarck", "incorrect_answers": ["Vladimir Ilyich Lenin", "Rudi Dutschke", "F.M. Dostoevsky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The plot of the famous Brodway musical West Side Story is based on which source?", "correct_answer": "Shakespears Romeo and Juliet", "incorrect_answers": ["The musical is a classical western", "The Bible", "A true story of two Los Angeles teenage gangs"]}]